Finding Aid for the Herbert Charles Sanborn Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Herbert Charles Sanborn Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0382
17.21 linear_feet
Feb. 18, 1873 Born in Winchester, Mass.
1896 PhB., Boston University
1897 A.M., Tufts College
1897-99 Teacher of Modern Languages, Concord, Mass. Academy
1900-01 Principla, Naugatuck High School
1901-02 Jacob Sleeper Fellow, Boston University
1902-06 Head Master in German of Bancroft School, Worcester, Mass.
Aug. 15, 1906 Married Edith May Tolles
1908 PhD., University of Munich (Magna cum laude)
1909-11 Professor of Philosophy and Psychology, Washington College, Chestertown, Md.
1911-42 Head, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, Vanderbilt University
1922-23 President, Southern Society for Philosophy and Psychology
1931-32 President, Andrew Jackson Chapter, Sons of the American Revolution
Additional info: Fellow, American Assn. for the Advancement of Science. Member: American Psychological Assn.; American Philosophical Assn.; British Institute of Philosophy; Gesellschaft fuer Aesthetik (Berlin).
July 7, 1967 Died
- Correspondence - Outgoing, October 24, 1934 - January 27, 1966; Outgoing correspondence of 129 letters. Chronologically arranged by days and months, letters are typescript, holograph, and carbon copies. Thirty-three undated letters found at end of outgoing correspondence. (Box 1, Folder 1-23)
- Correspondence - Incoming, Incoming correspondence of 4,326 letters, 235 post cards, and 70 telegrams. Alphabetically arranged, letters are typescript, holograph, and carbon copies. There are several circular and mimeographed. 1 Letters signed with initials only and with 1 name only are found at end. Illegible signatures found last.
  - Aall, Anathon (1), Feb. 28, 1925 (Box 1)
  - Abelite, August (2), Feb. 15, 1950, Feb. 16, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Abernathy, Raymond (1), April 29, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Achelis, Elisabeth (1), Oct. 24, 1946 (Box 1)
  - Acker, Sidney H. (1), Oct. 9, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Adair, George W. (4), Dec. 5, 1944, Dec. 14, 1944, Dec. 29, 1944, Apr. 19, 1945 (Box 1)
  - Adair, Mrs.George W. (1), Apr. 12, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Eva B. (1), Dec. 16, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Francis R., Jr. (2), Oct. 21, 1952, Nov. 13, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Frank (1), (n.d.) (Box 1)
  - Adams, Henry (1), Oct. 19, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Adler, Mrs. Helmut E. (1), Jan. 15, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Agish, Zahidallah (1), June 1, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Ahlgren, frank (1), Sept. 11, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Aid For Expellees And scapees, Inc. (1), Oct. 1, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Albany Capital District Dachshund Club (1), Sept. 30, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Aldahl, J.E. (2), Mar. 16, 1945; June 1, 1945 (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Will W. (3), June 3, 1942, Aug. 1, 1951, Sept. 28, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Allan, v. Maurice (2), Mar. 1;, 1951, Sept. 29, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Allen, Dolores (2), June 14, 1944 (post card), June 15, 1945 (Box 1)
  - Allen, Henry (1), Feb. 28, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Allen, Leroy (3), Jan. 28, 1941, Oct. 11, 1943, Sept. 15, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Allen, Philip J. (1), Jan. 9, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Allison, Buck (1), July 27, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Alluisi, Earl A. (2), June 20, 1962, Dec. 15, 1962 (Box 1)
  - Almon, Clopper (2), May 8, 1935, June 4, 1935 (Box 1)
  - Alne, Leonard A. (1), Dec. 13, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Amateur Fencers League of America (1), (n.d.) (Box 1)
  - American College Bureau (1), Nov. 2, 1944 (Box 1)
  - The American Dachshund (1), Oct. 6, 1951 (post card) (Box 1)
  - American Kennel Club (18), Sept. 13, 1943 (post card), Dec. 22, 1943 (pc), Dec. 27, 1943 (p.c.), Feb. 18, 1944 (p.c.), Mar. 10, 1944 (p.c.), Mar. 27, 1944 (p.c.); June 20, 1944 (p.c.), Aug. 3, 1944 (p.c.), Aug. 21, 1944 (p.c.), Sept. 7, 1944 (p.c.), Sept. 19, 1944 (p.c.); Oct. 21, 1944 (p.c.), Oct. 26, 1944 (p.c.), Nov. 4, 1944 (p.c.), Jan. 22, 1945 (p.c.), Mar. 20, 1945 (p.c.), July 17, 1945, July 25, 1945, Aug. 1, 1945, Aug. 10, 1945, Oct. 18, 1950 (telegram), (n.d.) (Box 1)
  - American Milk Goat Record Asso. (1), Feb. 23, 1945 (Box 1)
  - American Miniature Dachshund Association Incorporated (1), Sept. 7, 1950 (Box 1)
  - American Philosophical Association (9), Jan. 25, 1945, Apr. 19, 1945, Oct. 29, 1949, Oct. 20, 1950, Feb. 2, 1955, Apr. 1, 1957, May 29, 1958, (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 1)
  - Amstutz Hatcheries (1), Mar. 7, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Andersen, Carolyn H. (6), Sept. 12, 1951, Mar. 4, 1953, Aug. 15, 1953, Oct. 20, 1953, Apr. 24, 1954, Aug. 12, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Charles D. (1), May 2, 1944 (To Franklin C. Paschal) (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Melvin W. (1), Oct. 8, 1943 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, W.K. (1), Apr. 24, 1954 (telegram) (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Ramona (1), Dec. 31, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Anthofer, Frances (5), Feb. 26, 1945, Mar. 7, 1945, Mar. 7, 1945, Nov. 30, 1946 (telegram), Mar. 2 1 1948 (Box 1)
  - App, A.J. (2), Sept. 10, 1950, Oct. 18, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Armistead, Parkes (1), May 1, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Armitage, L. (1), Mar. 2, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, A.D. (1), June 29, 1931 (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, H.L. (1), April 3, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Arnold, Uee (3), Dec. 17, 1945, Mar. 2, 1946, Mar. 12, 1948 (Box 1)
  - Arnold, Edgar (1), June 5, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Artunoff, A. (1), July 14, 1960 (To Thurman Sensing) (Box 1)
  - Ascher, Mrs.W.F. (3), June 23, 1943, Sept. 17, 1943, Aug. 24, 1945 (Box 1)
  - Ashford, Monelle (1), Jan. 9, 1948 (Box 1)
  - Ashvorth, J.R. (1), 22, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Assmann, E. (1), Jan. 16, 1937 (Box 1)
  - Associates For Aaericanism (1), (N.D.) (Box 1)
  - Atkeson, Thomas Z. (4), Feb. 14, 1952, Feb. 26, 1952, Feb. 28, 1952, Mar. 4, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Atkins, Chuck (1), Jan. 15, 1956 (telegram) (Box 1)
  - Atkinson, H.J. (2), (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 1)
  - Atreya, B.L. (1), Feb. 7, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Aughenbaugh, W.L. (6), Jan. 31, 1946, Feb. 2, 1946, Feb. 14, 1946, Feb. 28, 1946, Mar. 25, 1946, Feb. 3, 1947 (Box 1)
  - Aughinbaugh, Sue E. (13), Aug. 23, 1945, Sept. 5, 1945, Sept. 20, 1945 (telegram), Sept. 20, 1945, Oct. 9, 1945, Oct. 14, 1945, Oct. 22, 1945, Oct. 31, 1945, Nov. 7, 1945, Jan. 3, 1946, Jan. 24, 1946, N.D.), (N.D.) (Box 1)
  - Aylvard, David A. (1), (N.D.) (Box 1)
  - Ayres, Harry Morgan (1), Apr. 12, 1929 (to L.S. McCormick) (Box 1)
  - Babb, J.J. (1), June 9, 1943 (Box 1)
  - Babcock, Gertrude Moseley (4), Sept. 16, 1952, Oct. 2, 1952, Feb. 18, 1960, Feb. 29, .L. 960 (Box 1)
  - Back, E.A. (1), Dec. 2, 1935 (Box 1)
  - Bagration, Rodam (1), Oct. 8, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Baha, Archie J. (4), Dec. 22, 1943 (post card), May 23, 1945 (post card), Nov. 15, 1952, (N.D.) (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Alice A. (1), July, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Betty W. (2), August 27, 1943, Feb. 2, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Ferriss c. (1), Sept. 7, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Bailey, oster (1), July, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Bailey, H.C. (1), June 2, 1960 (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Mrs. J.A.; (1), Apr. 13, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Baker, B.C. (1), Aug. 17., 1946 (Box 1)
  - Baker, E.M. (2), Dec., 1961, Jan., 1962 (Box 1)
  - Baldvin, A.L. (1), Dec. 13, 1950 (post card) (Box 1)
  - Bale, H.V. (3), June 1, 1943, Oct. 15, 1943, July 11, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Ball, Helen (1), Sept. 16, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Ballew, J.H. (1), July 22, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Balter, Bluford, H.J. (13), Feb. 25, 1955; Mar. 1, 1955, Mar. 3, 1955, Apr. 21, 1955, Apr. 29, 1955 (telegram), Hay 6, 1955, Jan. 18, 1956, Jan. 21,1956 (telegram), Mar. 6, 1956, (N.D.) (to Mr.Healey, letter includes 1 outgoing letter from Sanborn to Balter); Feb. 18, 1959, Mar. 25, 1959, Apr. 28 (N.D.) (telegram) (Box 1)
  - Balz, Albert G.A. (36), Feb. 23, 1934, Jan. 6, 1935, Jan. 30, 1935, May, 1935, Feb. 19, 1941, Apr. 20, 1942, July 14, 1942, Hay 3, 1944, June 27, 1944, Aug. 5, 1944, Sept. 8, 1944, Sept. 19, 1944, Oct. 5 1 1944 (To e.P. Heinlein), Nov. 10, 1944 (To c.P.Heinlein); Mar. 13, 1945, May 19, 1945, June 14, 1945 (To C.P. Heinlein), July 18, 1945, Aug. 1, 1945, Aug. 19, 1945 (To C.P.Heinlein); Apr. 8, 1946, Mar. 20, 1947, Jan. 18, 1950, Feb. 21, 1950, Mar. 12, 1950, Oct. 27, 1953, Dec. 1, 1953, Apr. 21, 1954; May 3, 1954, May 8, 1954, May 10, 1954, Aug. 3, 1954, Mar. 2, 1956, (N.D.), (N.D.) (Box 1)
  - Bandel, Robert (1), Dec. 28, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Banta, Mary Ellen (8), Oct. 5, 1946; Oct. 14, 1946, Nov. 4, 1946, Nov. 9, 1946, Dec. 19, 1946, Feb. 17, 1947, June 10, 1950, June 9, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Baptist, Mrs. Richard B. (1), Apr. 9, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Barnard AstronomicClub (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Barnes, H.E. (1), Oct. 12, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Harry E. (1), Dec. 2, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Barnett, Albert E. (1), Nov. 5, 1935 (Box 2)
  - Barr, John U. (1), July 18, 1955 (Box 2)
  - Barrow, Pebley E. (1), Jan. 25, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Barrows, Albert L. (5), Apr. 16, 1931, Aug. 27, 1931, Sept. 9, 1931, July 7, 1932, Apr. 5, 1933 (Box 2)
  - Barton, John w,.nn. (1), Feb. 28, 1928 (Box 2)
  - Baanerville, Jno. A. (1), Jan. 24, 1935 (Box 2)
  - Baas, Susanne (1), May 17, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Bate, John T. (2), June 7, 1954, June 22, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Bates, John G. (1), June 20, 1932 (Box 2)
  - Bates, Robert L. (1), June 19, 1926 (Box 2)
  - Batten, J. Minton (1), Mar. 23, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Bayliss, Charles A. (2), Nov. 7, 1952, Mar. 12, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Bean, L.L. (1), Hay 18, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Beck, Francis (1), Jan. 12, 1955 (To Gwynne Wisby, Wilma Hanna, Genie Howard) (Box 2)
  - Becker, A (8), Mar. 28, 1949, Sept. 30, 1949, Feb. 9, 1950, July 25, 1950, Sept. 3, 1950, Sept 9, 1950, Sept. 23, 1950, Nov. 1, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Becker, Bob (1), Jan. 24, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Bell, E.T. (1), Aug. 7 '1939 (post card) (Box 2)
  - Belle Meade Country Club (1), Hay 8, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Belser, T.A. (1), June 26, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Belser, Tom (5), June 14, 1951, July 9, 1951, Aug. 5, 1951, Sept. 14, 1951, Sept. 15, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Benckart, Robert G. (4), Apr. 4, 1950, May 22, 1950, June 1, 1950, June 28, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Benckart, Capt. and Mrs. Robert (1), Oct. 13, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Benedict, Clare (5), Feb. 8, May; 14, Nov. 9, .c. 8, (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Benkovitz, Miriam (1), Feb. 17, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Bennett, M. (1), May 9, 1949 (To Mary E. Banta) (Box 2)
  - Benaett, W.B. (8), Jan. 23, 1950, June 28, 1950, Aug. 4, 1950, Sept. 15, 1950, Oct. 23, 1950, Dec. 6, 1950, Dec. 7, 1950, ec. 28, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Benson, Maxwell (1), Apr. 26, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Bentien, Lydia (1), June 22, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Bentley, G.K. (2), Aug. 24, 1942, Feb. 2, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Bentley, Madison (5), Oct. 18, 1926, Mar. 13, 1929, Mar. 24, 1931, June 30, 1931, Sept. 27, 1935 (Box 2)
  - Bernstein, Leonard (1), Apr. 30, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Berresheim, Herbert H. (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Berry, Sarah C. (1), Oct. 22, 1948 (Box 2)
  - Bertrand, Herbert (1), June 17, 1935 (Box 2)
  - Bethune, Nagene Caapbell (16), Sept. and Oct., 1954, May 1955, July, 1955, Sept., 1955, Oct. 1955, Jan. 1956, Feb. 1956, May 1959, June, 1959, Sept. 1959, Jan.and Feb. 1961, Oct. 1962, Jan. (N.D.), Nov. and Dec. (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Bethurum, Dorothy (8), Apr. 24, 1941 (to the Chancellor and Trustees of Vanderbilt University),June 30, 1944, May 27, 1945, Oct. 18, 1949, Jan. 5, 1950, Sept. 25, 1952, Oct. 23, 1952, Oct. 26, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Beveridge, Catherine (9), Feb. 4, 1943, July 13, 1946, Mar. 20, 1947, Nov. 4, 1947 (telegram), Jan. 7, 1950 (to Mr. Meyers), Mar. 24, 1950, Dec. 4, 1950, Dec. 17, 1950, July 29 (Box 2)
  - Bevington, Elizabeth (1), Oct. 13, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Beward, J. (1), Feb. 7, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Beyer, Julia (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Bierly, H.E. (1), May 5, 1939 (Box 2)
  - Bigler, Francis A. (1), Jan. 15, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Billings, Mrs. Robert Shedden (2), Dec. 15, 1948, Nov. 3, 1949 (Box 2)
  - Billingsly, O. (1), July 13 (post card) (Box 2)
  - Billman, Carl (2), Apr. 21, 1952, Mar. 12, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Bingham, John L. (1), Mar. 16, 1955 (post card) (Box 2)
  - Bingham, W.V. (1), July 1, 1940 (Box 2)
  - Bird, Harrison, K. (1), Feb. 19, 1933 (Box 2)
  - Bisalaki, E.M. (1), Aug. 12, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Bishop, Aileen (1), Dec. 5, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Bixby, Henry D. (2), Oct. 20, 1949, Mar. 13, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Blackman, Mrs. E.B. (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Blackmore, John H. (1), Mar. 11, 1955 (Box 2)
  - Blake, Aldrich (1), Jan. 27, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Blanton, Lealie L. (1), Dec. 3, 1945 (post card) (Box 2)
  - Blau, George G.Jr. (1), Dec. 20, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Blayney, Lindsey (3), Feb. 14, 1925, (N.D.), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Bloch, Ingram (2), Apr. 14, 1952 (post card), Mar. 15, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Blochin, Ame Shzobeth (1), Apr. 10, 1932 (Box 2)
  - Blumen, Rinkey (1), Jan. 5, 1961 (to James. Stahlman) (Box 2)
  - Blumenthal, Erwin (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Boals, Bruce R. (1), Oct. 23, 1959 (post card) (Box 2)
  - Boas, George (1), Mar. 11, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Boeman, Tom (1), Sept. 5, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Bond, John B. (1), July 29, 1926 (Box 2)
  - Bond, Mrs.John B. (1), Dec. 4, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Bondurant, Alexander L. (1), Sept. 20, 1927 (Box 2)
  - Bonem, Frank L. (2), Oct. 20, 1951, Feb. 11, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Bonney, Marjorie (1), Nov. 14, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Boring, Edwin G. (1), April 7, 1953 (post card) (Box 2)
  - Bourland, A.P. (1), Oct. 3, 1924 (Box 2)
  - Bourland, Benjamin P. (1), July 16, 1942 (Box 2)
  - Bovie, Mrs. Holden (1), Apr. 10, 1935 (Box 2)
  - Bowers, Edgar and Helen (1), Jan. 9, 1935 (Box 2)
  - Bowman, Ethel (1), Jan. 23, 1931 (Box 2)
  - Boye, Gertrude L. (2), Sept. ll, 1943, Mar. 22, 1948 (Box 2)
  - Brady, Tom P. (1), June 8, 1955 (Box 2)
  - Bralliar, Floyd (2), Sept. 7, 1945, Feb. 6, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Bralliar, John S. (1), Aug. 1, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Brand, Albert R. (1), Apr. 15, 1932 (Box 2)
  - Branscomb, Harvie (8), Apr. 22, 1950, Nov. 27, 1950, Sept. 6, 1951, Dec. 19, 1951, llec. 10, 1956, July 2, 1957, July 16, 1957, May 27, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Breckinridge, Helen (1), Apr. 3, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Breckinridge, Scott D. Jr. (16), Nov. 18, 1949, Jan. 19, 1950, Feb. 10, 1950, Feb. 27, 1950 (to Albert Wolff), Oct. 27, 1950, Dec. 13, 1950; June 13, 1951, July 7, 1951, Dec. 5, 1951, Feb. 28, 1952, Oct. 27, 1952, Nov. 26, 1952, Dec. 11, 1952, Feb. 25, 1953; Mar. 12, 1953 (to Herbert Reisenfeld), Mar. 24, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Brewer, Virgil (2), Jan. 20, 1944, Jan. 24, 1947 (Box 2)
  - Brightman, Edgar, S. (25), Apr. 8, 1925, Apr. 13, 1925,17, 1925, July 28, 1925, Aug. 30, 1925, Dec. 15, 1925, Dec. 31, 1925, Apr. 22, 1926, Apr. 8, 1927, Feb. 8, 19Z8, Feb. 29, 1928, Nov. 22, 1929, June 1, 1934, Aug. 20, 1944 (post card), Oct. 20, 1944; Dec. 23, 1944 (post card), Apr. 9, 1950 (post card), Apr. 18, 1950 (to William Marshall Warren), Apr. 18, 1950, Aug!4, 1950, Aug. 16, 1950, Aug. 26, 1950, Sept. 3, 1950 (post card), Aug. 4, 1951, Sept. 3, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Briley, R.G. (1), Aug. 10, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Britton, Marguerite (1), Oct. 21, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Britzelmayr, Wilhelm (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Brockett, Bob (4), June 19, 1946, Nov. 26, 1946, July 10, 1950, Mar. 20, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Brockett, Mary Katherine (1), Aug. 10 (Box 2)
  - Brooks, J.G. (1), Feb. 9, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Brophy, Edward F. (1), May 1, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Brown, C.B. (1), Mar. 16, 1945 (post card) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Enoch (2), June 1, 1950, June 10, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Grace N. (10), Mar. 9, 1946, Feb. 14, 1950, Mar. 8, 1951, Apr. 12, 1951, Mar. 22, 1952, May 12, 1953, Sept. 15, 1954, Oct. 12, 1954, July 28, 1955, (M.D.) (Box 2)
  - Brown, Leslie C. (3), Jan. 4, 1955, Jan. 17, 1955 (to Robert Lanier Hudgins), Feb. 16, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Lolita (1), July 31, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Philip Marshall (2), Oct. 27, 1952, Sept. 3, 1955 (Box 2)
  - Brown, William H. (2), June 21, 1951, (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Browning, Gordon (1), Oct. 8, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, Sara C. (5), May 27, 1954 (post card), Dec. 15, 1958, Aug. 14, 1959, Dec. 1, 1959, Jan. 28, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Bruhl, Lucien Levy (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Brullman, Rob (1), Jan. 2, 1925 (Box 2)
  - Brumberg, Sabine (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Bryant, L.E. (1), May 24, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Bryant, Lydia and Norman (1), Dec. 20, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Bryant, Norman (1), Aug 27 1943 (Box 2)
  - Bryson, Fred R. (4), Oct. 14, 1943, Sept. 12, 1950, ec. 11, 1950, Apr. 7, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Bryaon, Mrs. Fred (2), Aug. 24, 1951, Oct. 18, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Buchanan, John W. (1), May 15, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Buchhard, F. (1), Feb. 16, 1949 (Box 2)
  - Buchner, Edward F. (1), May 19, 1925 (Box 2)
  - Buck, C,A. (1), June 29, 1926 (Box 2)
  - Buckinghan, Hugh E. (1), Apr. 13, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Buckley, Wm. F. Jr. (3), Nov. 23, 1955; July 6, 1959, Mar. 15, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Buford, Thomas B. (1), Aug. 23, 1955 (Box 2)
  - Bulkley, E.W. (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Bunch, Marion E. (4), Mar. 3, 1950, Mar. 14, 1950, May 21, 1956, Feb. 1, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Bundy, Edgar, C. (2), Mar. 3, 1959, (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Bunnell, Mrs. Donald (1), July 12, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Buquo, H.C. (1), Nov. 19,1952 (Box 2)
  - Burch, Lucius E. Jr. (1), r. 3, 1940 (Box 2)
  - Burdick, Kathryn (1), Nov. 1, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Burleson, T.O.K. (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Burns, John J. (1), Hay 12, 1936 (Box 2)
  - Burrow, William (1), Aug. 18, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Bursey, Joseph A. (1), Dec. 4, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Burton, R. King (5), Oct. 27, 1943, Nov. 4, 1943, Aug. 20, 1945, Jan. 22, 1952, Mar. 7, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Bush, Prescott (1), Sept. 17, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Butler, W.D. (1), May 5, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Byrnes, James F. (1), May 31, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Byrns, Joseph W. Jr. (2), April 10, 1946, Sept. 11, 1949 (Box 2)
  - Byrom, Robert (1), Jan. 25, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Cahoon, Willie G. (1), Nov. 20, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Cain, Mary D. (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Calder, Curtis E. (1), Feb. 19, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Caldwell, Willis (2), Aug. 31, 1959, Nov. 9, 1959 (Box 2)
  - Callahan, E.B. (1), Jan. 5, 1922 (Box 2)
  - Callanan, Ruth M. (1), July 27, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Campbell, Gladys (1), Nov. 13, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Caapbell, J.w. (6), Nov. 17, 1943, Nov. 15, 1945, Nov. 30, 1945, Jan. 7, 1946, Aug. 30, 1946, Nov. 25, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Canada, Arthur A. (1), (N.D.) (Box 2)
  - Campbell, John Neal (2), June 28, 1945, July 31, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Cannon, James Jr. (1), July 27, 1925 (Box 2)
  - Capen, Samuel P. (1), Oct. 12, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Carlin, Leo P. (1), Dec. 2, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Carlson, Edgar M. (1), Jan. 17, 1945 (Box 2)
  - Carmichael, Leonard (10), Nov. 3, 1927, Jan. 15, 1932, Apr. 20, 1942, Jan. 5, 1950 (post card), Nov. 21, 1951 (post card), Oct. 15, 1952, Apr. 21, 1959, May 6, 1959, Nov. 20, 1959, Mar. 16, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Carmichael, O.C. (4), Feb. 5, 1941, Feb. 5, 1942, Oct. 25, 1946, Oct. 29, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Carmichael, Peter A. (11), July 2, 1943; Sept. 14, 1945, July 9, 1946, Nov. 29, 1949,. Feb. 17, 1950, Feb. 23, 1950, Mar. 8, 1950, Mar. 18, 1950, Mar. 31, 1950, Dec. 14, 1960, Jan. 14, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Carney, Helen and Robert (1), Dec. 20, 1944 (post card) (Box 3)
  - Carney, James H. (1), July 18, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Carre, Henry Beach (1), Apr. 12, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Carre, Henry Beach,, Mrs. (1), (N.D.) (Box 3)
  - Carter, Andrev J. (1), (N.D.) (post card) (Box 3)
  - Carter, Clara Mae (1), Oct. 9, 1951 (to Judge C.Havard Bozeman, Com. W.H. Bi11 Maynard, and embers of Knox County Court) (Box 3)
  - Carter, Mary Lynn (1), Feb. 4, 1949 (Box 3)
  - Carta, Willis (1), Sept. 10, 1955 (to Mr. Blake) (Box 3)
  - Case, Arthur E. (1), Jan. 11, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Case, Harold C. (1), Dec. 1952 (Box 3)
  - Castello Fencing Equipment (1), May 3, 1935 (telegram) (Box 3)
  - Castello, Hugo M. (4), Sept. 12, 1949, Mar. 6, 1950, Jan. 7, 1952, Feb. 19, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Castello, James H. (1), (N.D.) (Box 3)
  - Castrino, Helene (3), Dec. 13, 1933, Jan. 25, 1935, May 6, 1935 (Box 3)
  - Casvell, Mrs. C (17), Oct. 13, 1943 (post card), Oct. 18, 1943 (post card), Oct. 27, 1943, Nov. 22, 1943, Dec. 7, 1943, Dec. 18, 1943, Feb. 15, 1944, Mar, 14, 1944 (post card), Apr. 22, 1944, June 27, 1944, June 29, 1944 (post card); Aug. 9, 1944, Aug. 23, 1944 (post card), Aug. 31, 1944, ept. 9, 1944, Mar. 14, 1945 (post card), Apr. 4, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Caswell, Mr. and Mrs. C. (3), Sept. 6, 1943, Sept. 24, 1943, Dec. 17, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Caswell, Lucille (1), Dec. 17, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Cantalano, Bee R. (2), Apr. 14, 1946, Jan. 21, 1947 (Box 3)
  - Cattell, Jaques (7), May 18, 1950, July 28, 1950, Aug. 15, 1951, (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Causey, James D. (2), Oct. 26, 1954, Nov. 8, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Ceccato, Silvio (1), July 2, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Cellarius, Justine (1), Sept. 16, 1943 (Box 3)
  - Celli, Anne (1), July 1, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Chang, Diana (1), July 5, 1951 (Box 3)
  - Chapman, B.J. (1), June 22, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Chaashacy, F. (1), (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Chateau, Josef (7), Jan. 16, 1951 (to the American Kennel Club), Apr. 6, 1951, Apr. 17, 1952, Feb. 18, 1953, Aug. 14, 1953, July 15, 1954, (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Chavenon Society (1), (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Cheda, Isabella (1), Nov. 10, 1949 (Box 3)
  - Cheney, Frances (13), Dec. 22, 1943, Hay 31, 1944, Jan. 20, 1945 (post card), Jan. 25, 1945, Feb. 1, 1945, Mar. 24, 1945, Apr. 7, 19 5, Apr,.o' 24, 1945, May 2, 1946, Mar. 18, 1954 (post card), Juiy 6, 1954 (post card), Aug. 11, 1955, (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Chickering, Edward C. (1), Sept. 13, 1933 (Box 3)
  - Chilton, W.B. (5), Jan. 5, 1951, Jan. 9, 1951, Jan. 31, 1951 (to the Editor of the Banner), Feb. 22, 1951, Oct. 4, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Chisholm, Roderick H. (1), May 25, 1957 (Box 3)
  - Christopher, Arthur J. (1), Feb. 14, 1952 (Box 3)
  - Churchman, C. West (1), Oct. 1, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Clark, Belle D. (3), Oct. 21, 1952, Nov. 11, 1952, Mar 25, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Clark, Blake (1), (n.d.) (post card) (Box 3)
  - Clark, Mr. and Mrs. Blake (1), Nov. 10, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Clark, Charles B. (4), Oct. 15, 1943, Aug. 29, 1950, Mar. 16, 1953, Sept. 29, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Clark, Frank W. (3), Sept. 7, 1955, Sept. 7, 1955, Oct. 26, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Clark, Harry (1), Mar. 31, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Clark, Sam L. (2), Apr. 17, 1945, Aug. 4, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Clegg, Sarline (1), Dec. 9, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Clemens, Cyril (1), Dec. 19, 1944 (Box 3)
  - Clement, Frank G. (1), Apr. 7, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Cliffov, Jack (1), Aug. 22, 1935 (Box 3)
  - Clifton, Freda M. (1), Sept. 4, 1952 (Box 3)
  - Clince, Mrs. Chas. (1), Oct. 17, 1950 (post card) (Box 3)
  - Close, Upton (12), June 29, 1945, Sept. 17, 1945, Sept. 2, 1945, Oct. 1, 1945, Oct. 8, 1945, Feb. 22, 1946, Feb. 25, 1946, Apr. 1, 1946, May 4, 1946, Aug. 1, 1951, Aug. 30, 1951, (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Cobb. Mary (64), Jan. 20, 1940, Apr. 24, 1944 (telegram), Apr. 25, 1944, May 9, 1944, May 11, 1944 (post card), May 18, 1944, June 28, 1944, July 13, 1944, July 17, 1944 (post card), Aug. 10, 1944, Oct. 16, 1944, Jan. 30, 1945, Feb. 12, 1945, May 7, 1945; Aug. 8, 1945, Aug. 26, 1945, Sept. 17, 1945, Sept. 18, 1945, Oct. 16, 1945, Nov. 16, 1945, Nov. 26, 1945, Dec. 1, 1945 (post card), ec. 31, 1945, Jan. 4, 1946, Jan. 5, 1946 (post card), Feb. 14, 1946, Feb. 18, 1946, Apr. 2, 1946; Apr. 28, 1946, pr. 29, 1946, May 23, 1946 (post card), May 23, 1946, June 4, 1946 (post card), June 9, 1946, June 13, 1946, ept. 2, 1946 (post card), ept. 5, 1946, ept. 28, 1946, Oct. 12, 1946; Nov. 6, 1946, Nov. 12, 1946, Nov. 13, 1946, Nov. 27, 1946, Dec. 5, 1946, Vee. 12, 1946, (post card), Dec. 31, 1946, Jan. 11, 1947, Mar. 4, 1947, Mar. 9, 1947, Mar. 25, 1947, Apr. 7, 1947; Jan. 19, 1948, Feb. 19, 1950 (post card),, Apr. 26, 1950, June 12, 1950, June 26, 1950, Uec. 19, 1950, Apr. 4, 1951, July 22, (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Coburn, Bessie Street (2), June 21, 1954, July 27, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Coffey, Barry (1), Dec. 21, 1943 (Box 3)
  - Cohen, Joe (1), May 31, 1953 (Box 3)
  - Cokessn, J. (1), July 23, 19o6 (post card) (to F. Chasshacy) (Box 3)
  - Colby, Frank O. (5), Sept. 10, 1945, Oct. 6, 1945, Nov. 14, 1945, Jan. 11, 1949, Oct. 9, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Cole, Ada A. (1), (n.d.) (Box 3)
  - Cole, C.C. (1), Feb. 17, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Cole, Helen Moore (1), Oct. 19, 1948 (Box 3)